Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
"Love in the Moonlight" (Episode 9)
"الحب في ضوء القمر" (الحلقة 9)
Are you sure that this is Prince Saenkaew's handwriting?
هل أنت متأكد أن هذه هي خط يد الأمير ساينكاو؟
Nual said that she just cleaned up Prince Saenkaew's room and dropped this.
قالت نوال أنها قامت للتو بتنظيف غرفة الأمير ساينكاو وأسقطت هذا.
Why did he need to write a letter to Sasin?
لماذا كان عليه أن يكتب رسالة إلى ساسين؟
You saw that they were so close.
لقد رأيت أنهم كانوا قريبين جدًا.
But when Sasin got shot and hospitalized,
ولكن عندما أصيب ساسين برصاصة وتم نقله إلى المستشفى،
Prince Saenkaew never once went to see him.
لم يذهب الأمير ساينكاو لرؤيته ولو مرة واحدة.
Don't you think it's strange?
ألا تعتقد أن الأمر غريب؟
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I think there's something weird going on between them.
أعتقد أن هناك شيئًا غريبًا يحدث بينهما.
You think people would praise your love?
هل تعتقد أن الناس سوف يمتدحون حبك؟
You will be a clown
سوف تكون مهرجًا
and everyone will be laughing at you.
وسوف يضحك عليك الجميع.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
Are you gonna judge me as well?
هل ستحكم علي أيضا؟
Our son hates me right now.
ابننا يكرهني الآن.
I've become a devil
لقد أصبحت شيطانًا
who gets in a way of his happiness.
من يقف في طريق سعادته.
Come in.
ادخل.
Prince Bodin told me to invite you for a discussion.
لقد طلب مني الأمير بودان أن أدعوك لمناقشة.
He wanted to talk about some details of the wedding.
أراد التحدث عن بعض تفاصيل الزفاف.
My workers have done drafting
لقد قام عمالي بالصياغة
the layout for the wedding venue.
تخطيط مكان حفل الزفاف.
Please have a look.
من فضلك ألقي نظرة.
If you would like to add anything, just let me know.
إذا كنت ترغب في إضافة أي شيء، فقط اسمحوا لي أن أعرف.
If you think it's fine, then I'm fine with it.
إذا كنت تعتقد أن الأمر على ما يرام، فأنا موافق على ذلك.
About the business in Chiang Mai,
حول الأعمال التجارية في شيانغ ماي،
my people also decorated a house for newlyweds.
كما قام شعبي بتزيين منزل للعروسين.
They can move in right after the wedding.
بإمكانهم الإنتقال للعيش معًا مباشرةً بعد الزفاف.
Did you hire a clerk to work at your company in Chiang Mai?
هل قمت بتعيين كاتب للعمل في شركتك في شيانغ ماي؟
I'd like to refer one person to work.
أرغب في إحالة شخص واحد للعمل.
You can refer more than one people. The business is new.
يمكنك إحالة أكثر من شخص. العمل جديد.
I need many employees to work there.
أحتاج إلى العديد من الموظفين للعمل هناك.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
Can we refer Sasin to work there?
هل يمكننا توجيه ساسين للعمل هناك؟
Sasin can take care of Pin.
ساسين يستطيع الاعتناء ببين.
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
When she is married to Saenkaew,
عندما تزوجت من ساينكاو،
my son can take care of her.
ابني يستطيع الاعتناء بها.
The others don't need to follow them.
لا يحتاج الآخرون إلى اتباعهم.
Okay, I'll let you decide.
حسنًا، سأترك لك القرار.
Are you thinking about your nephew?
هل تفكر في ابن أخيك؟
That's right. His wedding is getting closer.
هذا صحيح. زفافه يقترب.
If we can't stop them, we are in big trouble.
إذا لم نتمكن من إيقافهم، فسنكون في مشكلة كبيرة.
Are you sure
هل أنت متأكد
that Prince Kamfah ordered someone to shoot that musician?
أن الأمير كامفاه أمر شخصًا بإطلاق النار على هذا الموسيقي؟
Why would he do that for?
لماذا يفعل ذلك؟
Oh my goodness! Eww!
يا إلهي! إيووه!
Honey, look at this!
عزيزتي، أنظري إلى هذا!
- What is it? - Here.
- ما هو؟ - هنا.
So disgusting.
مقزز للغاية.
A wedding of two men.
حفل زفاف رجلين.
They aren't afraid of people gossipping.
إنهم لا يخافون من ثرثرة الناس.
People these days like to do strange things.
الناس في هذه الأيام يحبون القيام بأشياء غريبة.
Man marrying another man?
الرجل يتزوج رجلا آخر؟
Saenkaew?
ساينكاو؟
What're you doing? People can see us.
ماذا تفعل؟ الناس يستطيعون رؤيتنا.
Holy sh...!
يا إلهي...!
Or…Saenkaew…
أو…ساينكايو…
- and his future bride's cousin? - What is it?
- وابن عم زوجته المستقبلية؟ - ما هو؟
What are they?
ما هم؟
At the restaurant the other day,
في المطعم في اليوم الآخر،
we saw them hugging like this.
لقد رأيناهم يتعانقون هكذا.
They can't possible be anything else but…
لا يمكن أن يكونوا أي شيء آخر غير...
Really close friends, right?
أصدقاء مقربين حقًا، أليس كذلك؟
Oh honey!
اوه عزيزتي!
They are lovers.
إنهم عشاق.
But bravo to you.
ولكن برافو لك.
Brilliant!
باهِر!
That's why.
لهذا السبب.
Saenkaew has never been rumored with any women.
لم تنتشر أي شائعات عن علاقة ساينكاو بأي امرأة على الإطلاق.
He is gay, he is queer.
إنه مثلي الجنس، إنه غريب.
He likes men.
انه يحب الرجال.
Disgusting.
مقزز.
So Prince Kamfah ordered someone to kill his son's boyfriend
فأمر الأمير كامفاه بقتل صديق ابنه
because he's afraid that the wedding'd be off, right?
لأنه خائف من إلغاء حفل الزفاف، أليس كذلك؟
This is huge. It's not only ruining the wedding,
هذا أمرٌ ضخم. إنه لا يُفسد حفل الزفاف فحسب،
but my brother will also be humiliated
ولكن أخي سوف يهان أيضا
all the way from Bangkok to Chansaeng.
طوال الطريق من بانكوك إلى تشانسينغ.
The best!
الأفضل!
Now, it's my turn.
الآن جاء دوري.
Are you sure about this? Let's go to our house.
هل أنت متأكد من هذا؟ لنذهب إلى منزلنا.
Why are you living with Sanya?
لماذا تعيش مع سانيا؟
But there are only females in your house.
ولكن لا يوجد في منزلك سوى الإناث.
It'd be better for him to stay with men.
سيكون من الأفضل له أن يبقى مع الرجال.
Sanya and Mingmitr are living there.
سانيا ومينغميتر يعيشون هناك.
They can help him clean up.
يمكنهم مساعدته في التنظيف.
Also, their rental house is closed to the hospital.
كما أن منزلهم المستأجر قريب من المستشفى.
He can visit the hospital to clean his wound easily.
يمكنه زيارة المستشفى لتنظيف جرحه بسهولة.
I won't stay there for too long.
لن أبقى هناك لفترة طويلة.
When my wound is healed, I'll go back home.
عندما يشفى جرحي سأعود إلى المنزل.
Don't you worry about him.
لا تقلق عليه .
We're gonna take the best care of him.
سنحرص على رعايته على أكمل وجه.
My wedding is in three days.
حفل زفافي بعد ثلاثة أيام.
You need to be there.
يجب عليك أن تكون هناك.
You represent my mother.
أنت تمثل والدتي.
I want you there, on my happiest day.
أريدك هناك، في يومي الأكثر سعادة.
We should go
ينبغي علينا أن نذهب
before the traffic hits.
قبل أن تصل حركة المرور إلى ذروتها.
Help him out of here.
ساعده على الخروج من هنا.
Let me help you with that.
دعني أساعدك في ذلك.
Sasin was discharged from the hospital today.
خرج ساسين من المستشفى اليوم.
I heard that he'll stay with his musician friends.
سمعت أنه سيبقى مع أصدقائه الموسيقيين.
He must be so scared.
لابد أنه خائف جدًا.
Good.
جيد.
The wedding will go smoothly.
سيكون حفل الزفاف سلسًا.
And it will end.
وسوف ينتهي.
My dearest Saenkaew,
عزيزي ساينكاو،
You're not the one who go through this.
أنت لست الشخص الذي يمر بهذا.
I'm right here.
انا هنا .
I won't let go of your hands.
لن أترك يديك.
I know that you're in pain.
أعلم أنك في ألم.
Trust me when I say that I understand it.
ثق بي عندما أقول لك أنني أفهم ذلك.
I understand what you're going through.
أنا أفهم ما تمر به.
I understand your fear.
انا أفهم خوفك.
But I want you to know
ولكن أريدك أن تعرف
that you don't need to carry it all by yourself.
أنك لست بحاجة إلى حملها كلها بنفسك.
You still have me. I love and care for you more than my own life.
مازلتُ أملكك. أحبك وأهتم بك أكثر من حياتي.
I don't want you to feel guilty
لا أريدك أن تشعر بالذنب
or feel like you're fighting this on your own.
أو تشعر وكأنك تقاتل هذا الأمر بمفردك.
This is our story
هذه قصتنا
and we'll begin this together.
وسوف نبدأ هذا معًا.
Wait for me a little longer
انتظرني قليلا
and I'll try to find way for you and Ms. Rachawadee to get
وسأحاول أن أجد طريقة لك وللسيدة راشاوادي للوصول إلى
marriage certificate before your wedding day.
شهادة الزواج قبل يوم زفافك.
I'll do anything for us to be together.
سأفعل أي شيء لنكون معًا.
While we're away and you're missing me,
بينما نحن بعيدون وأنت تفتقدني،
please look up to see the moon.
من فضلك انظر إلى الأعلى لرؤية القمر.
Please know that we're looking at the same moon.
يرجى العلم أننا ننظر إلى نفس القمر.
Why did Ms. Rachawadee tell Sasin to live with us?
لماذا طلبت السيدة راشاوادي من ساسين أن يعيش معنا؟
And she asked us to watch out for his safety.
وطلبت منا أن نحرص على سلامته.
She might be worried that he could come back to hurt Sasin.
ربما تكون قلقة من أنه قد يعود لإيذاء ساسين.
We live together so we can watch out for Sasin.
نحن نعيش معًا حتى نتمكن من مراقبة ساسين.
Why didn't he stay in the palace? So many people than this place.
لماذا لم يبق في القصر؟ هناك أناسٌ أكثر من هذا المكان.
It's safer that way.
إنه أكثر أمانا بهذه الطريقة.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
You need to watch Sasin.
يجب عليك مراقبة ساسين.
Let me know when he's alone.
أخبرني عندما يكون وحيدًا.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Your nephew and that man live in different places like this,
ابن أخيك وذلك الرجل يعيشان في أماكن مختلفة مثل هذا،
how can we expose them?
كيف يمكننا كشفهم؟
Don't worry, the lovers will try
لا تقلق، العشاق سوف يحاولون
to find their ways back together.
للعثور على طريقهم معًا مرة أخرى.
The other one is injured and nearly dead.
والآخر مصاب ويكاد أن يموت.
So he will try his best to find him.
لذلك سوف يبذل قصارى جهده للعثور عليه.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I have my way to stimulate them to meet eventually.
لدي طريقتي لتحفيزهم على الالتقاء في نهاية المطاف.
What do you think, Homthip?
ماذا تعتقد يا هومثيب؟
He looks good.
إنه يبدو جيدا.
After the western ceremony,
بعد الحفل الغربي،
there will be a Chansaeng traditional ceremony.
سيكون هناك حفل تشانساينج التقليدي.
He needs to try on a traditional outfit.
يحتاج إلى تجربة الزي التقليدي.
Right.
يمين.
You look so good.
أنت تبدو جيدا جدا.
It's too bad. Your mom should have
إنه أمر مؤسف. كان ينبغي على والدتك
seen you in your wedding day.
لقد رأيتك في يوم زفافك.
The happiest day of your life.
أسعد يوم في حياتك.
What's wrong? Why're you crying?
ما بك؟ لماذا تبكي؟
Tell me, what is it?
أخبرني ما هو؟
Why're you crying?
لماذا تبكي؟
You need to be careful when you're alone.
يجب عليك أن تكون حذرا عندما تكون وحدك.
Don't open the door to anyone besides us.
لا تفتح الباب لأحد غيرنا.
Okay.
تمام.
We need to take care of VIP guests at the club,
نحن بحاجة إلى رعاية الضيوف المهمين في النادي،
otherwise, we wouldn't have left you here alone.
لولا ذلك لما تركناك هنا وحدك.
Come on.
تعال.
I'm a man now, I can take care of myself.
أنا رجل الآن، وأستطيع الاعتناء بنفسي.
You two should get going already.
ينبغي لكما أن تبدآ بالذهاب بالفعل.
- Go. - Fine.
- اذهب. - حسنًا.
See you.
أرك لاحقًا.
You need to find someone to
تحتاج إلى العثور على شخص ما
watch the entrace on the wedding day.
شاهد المدخل في يوم الزفاف.
Don't let Inthorn or Kalong get into the ceremony.
لا تسمح لـ Inthorn أو Kalong بالدخول إلى الحفل.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Are you Prince Saenkaew?
هل أنت الأمير ساينكاو؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Who are you? How did you get in here?
من أنت؟ كيف دخلت إلى هنا؟
I'm Sasin's friend.
أنا صديق ساسين.
I sneaked in here to look for you.
لقد تسللت إلى هنا للبحث عنك.
Sasin's condition is getting worse
حالة ساسين تتدهور
he's about to die.
إنه على وشك الموت.
What?
ماذا؟
He said that he wanted to see you.
وقال أنه يريد رؤيتك.
You need to go and see him right now.
يجب عليك أن تذهب لرؤيته الآن.
Saenkaew is running away. Hurry!
ساينكاو يهرب. أسرع!
Prince Saenkaew?
الأمير ساينكاو؟
Who is he running after?
من يركض خلفه؟
Prince Kamfah?
الأمير كامفاه؟
What are they doing?
ماذا يفعلون؟
- Hey! Follow them. - Yes, sir.
- هيا! اتبعهم. - نعم سيدي.
Hello? Let's try the camera, honey.
مرحباً؟ لنجرب الكاميرا يا عزيزتي.
So pretty.
جميلة جداً.
One more shot.
طلقة اخرى
How was it?
كيف وجدته؟
- Very chic, honey. - Oh well.
- أنيقة جدًا يا عزيزتي. - حسنًا.
When Saenkaew comes here to see Sasin,
عندما يأتي ساينكاو إلى هنا لرؤية ساسين،
I'll snap their photos when they're in love.
سألتقط صورهم عندما يقعون في الحب.
And I'll expose the photos at his wedding.
وسأعرض الصور في حفل زفافه.
His bride will be so mad and will call off the wedding.
ستكون عروسه غاضبة جدًا وستلغي حفل الزفاف.
Sounds like a good plan.
يبدو وكأنه خطة جيدة.
But it takes days to develop these photos.
لكن الأمر يستغرق أيامًا لتطوير هذه الصور.
Don't you think the wedding will be over once we get the photos?
ألا تعتقد أن حفل الزفاف سينتهي بمجرد حصولنا على الصور؟
Why don't they have a camera that can show photos immediately?
لماذا لا يوجد لديهم كاميرا يمكنها عرض الصور فورًا؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
They're here, let's hide.
إنهم هنا، دعونا نختبئ.
Sasin is living inside.
ساسين يعيش في الداخل.
Let's go, honey.
دعنا نذهب يا عزيزتي.
- Who's that? - It's me.
- من هذا؟ - أنا.
Saenkaew?
ساينكاو؟
Saenkaew!
ساينكاو!
I'm not dreaming, am I?
أنا لا أحلم، أليس كذلك؟
- This one? - That's right.
- هذا؟ - هذا صحيح.
- Inthorn? - You scared me! Kamfah?
- إنثورن؟ - لقد أفزعتني! كامفاه؟
- How did you get here?
- كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟
You?
أنت؟
You planned to kidnap my son?
هل خططت لاختطاف ابني؟
Kidnap your son?
إختطاف ابنك؟
Why would I do that?
لماذا أفعل ذلك؟
Tell me, what's you plan?
أخبرني ما هي خطتك؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Phong! Get up!
فونغ! انهض!
What do you think you're doing?
ماذا تعتقد أنك تفعل؟
How're you feeling?
كيف حالك؟
Still hurt?
هل لازلت تتألم؟
Tell me! Where are you hiding my son?
أخبرني! أين تخبئ ابني؟
Tell me!
أخبرني!
I didn't hide Saenkaew anywhere.
لم أخفي ساينكاو في أي مكان.
Right now, he must be
الآن يجب أن يكون
making out with Sasin, his boyfriend.
التقبيل مع ساسين، صديقه.
What're you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
You didn't expect me to find out about this, did you?
لم تتوقع مني أن أعرف هذا، أليس كذلك؟
I'm not sure about it first
أنا لست متأكد من ذلك أولاً
but seeing your face right now, makes me
لكن رؤية وجهك الآن يجعلني
realize that my guess is right.
أدركت أن تخميني صحيح.
- Stop talking nonsense already. - What nonsense?
- توقف عن الكلام الهراء الآن. - ما هذا الهراء؟
You already knew about it, didn't you?
لقد كنت تعرف ذلك بالفعل، أليس كذلك؟
That there's something going on between Saenkaew and Sasin,
أن هناك شيئًا يحدث بين ساينكاو وساسين،
- that's why you sent someone to hurt him. - What?
- لهذا السبب أرسلت شخصًا لإيذائه. - ماذا؟
Oh my goodness!
يا إلهي!
Prince Bodin is joining the party as well?
هل ينضم الأمير بودين إلى الحفلة أيضًا؟
What a surprise!
يا لها من مفاجأة!
What does it mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
You know what? When I got shot,
هل تعلم ماذا؟ عندما أُصبت برصاصة،
I wasn't afraid of death,
لم أكن خائفا من الموت،
I was afraid that I couldn't see your face again.
كنت خائفة من أن لا أستطيع رؤية وجهك مرة أخرى.
I'm worried that my dad will hurt you again.
أنا قلق من أن والدي سوف يؤذيك مرة أخرى.
If that's the case, then I'd rather give you up,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، فأنا أفضل أن أتخلى عنك،
than having something happen to you.
من أن يحدث لك شيء ما.
I won't give up.
أنا لن أستسلم.
And you can't give up either.
ولا يمكنك الاستسلام أيضًا.
Okay?
تمام؟
Well, why did you ask him that?
حسنًا، لماذا سألته ذلك؟
You expected to get the truth?
هل كنت تتوقع الحصول على الحقيقة؟
You should have asked me.
كان ينبغي عليك أن تسألني.
Sasin was shot and almost died
تم إطلاق النار على ساسين وكاد أن يموت
because of my brother.
بسبب أخي.
He was so furious
لقد كان غاضبا جدا
that Saenkaew is having an intimate relationship with Sasin.
أن ساينكاو لديه علاقة حميمة مع ساسين.
Come on, brother?
تعال يا أخي؟
You know it well that your son doesn't like women
أنت تعلم جيدًا أن ابنك لا يحب النساء
still you tried
لا تزال تحاول
to get him to marry Prince Bodin's daughter.
ليتزوج ابنة الأمير بودان.
This is a fraud.
هذه عملية احتيال.
Is it true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
It's not true. Prince Inthorn is lying.
هذا ليس صحيحًا. الأمير إنثورن يكذب.
Stop talking.
توقف عن الكلام
We should go and see them with our own eyes.
ينبغي لنا أن نذهب ونراهم بأعيننا.
Saenkaew is now hanging out with Sasin,
Saenkaew يتسكع الآن مع Sasin،
after not seeing him for such a long time.
بعد أن لم أراه لفترة طويلة.
Perhaps they are making out right now.
ربما هم يقومون بالتقبيل الآن.
If you want to see them, please follow me.
إذا كنت تريد رؤيتهم، يرجى متابعتي.
Let's go, honey.
دعنا نذهب يا عزيزتي.
But you can't sneak out to see me like this again,
ولكن لا يمكنك التسلل لرؤيتي بهذه الطريقة مرة أخرى،
your dad could catch you.
والدك قد يمسك بك.
Wait?
انتظر؟
You told your friend to tell me
لقد طلبت من صديقك أن يخبرني
that you're in severe condition, didn't you?
أنك في حالة خطيرة، أليس كذلك؟
I didn't.
لم أكن.
Sasin!
ساسين!
Saenkaew! Open the door!
ساينكاو! افتح الباب!
Sasin! Saenkaew!
ساسين! ساينكاو!
I know that you two are making…
أعلم أنكما تقومان بـ...
out right now.
خارج الآن.
I…
أنا…
What're you doing here?
ماذا تفعل هنا؟
Saenkaew and I are here to see Sasin.
أنا وساينكايو هنا لرؤية ساسين.
Not true. Sasin and Saenkaew are lovers.
غير صحيح. ساسين وساينكايو عاشقان.
They're fooling you, Pin-anong.
إنهم يخدعونك يا بين أنونج.
No way.
مستحيل.
Sasin is a cousin that I love so much.
ساسين هو ابن عمي الذي أحبه كثيرًا.
He won't break my heart for sure.
لن يكسر قلبي بالتأكيد.
See? There's nothing like what Inthorn said earlier.
أرأيت؟ لا يوجد شيء مثل ما قاله إنثورن سابقًا.
What should we do?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل؟
What do you think? We need to leave.
ماذا تعتقد؟ علينا أن نغادر.
Saenkaew,
ساينكاو،
I don't believe you. I will find a proof for this.
لا أصدقك. سأجد دليلاً على ذلك.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Prince Inthorn can't be trusted for one second, always a messy one.
لا يمكن الوثوق بالأمير إنثورن ولو لثانية واحدة، فهي دائمًا ثانية فوضوية.
Pin, Saenkaew, are you leaving with me?
بين، ساينكاو، هل ستغادر معي؟
I'm gonna stay for a bit longer.
سأبقى لفترة أطول قليلاً.
I need to discuss something with Sasin about the wedding.
أريد أن أناقش شيئًا مع ساسين بخصوص حفل الزفاف.
Should we go then?
هل يجب علينا أن نذهب إذن؟
- So they can talk about the wedding. - Sure.
- حتى يتمكنوا من التحدث عن حفل الزفاف. - بالتأكيد.
Would you like to ride with me back home?
هل ترغب في الركوب معي إلى المنزل؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Pin?
دبوس؟
Thank you for…
شكرا لك على…
You think that I'm stupid?
هل تعتقد أنني غبي؟
Pin.
دبوس.
My dearest Saenkaew.
عزيزتي ساينكاو.
One hour earlier.
قبل ساعة واحدة.
Saenkaew?
ساينكاو؟
Are you still up?
هل مازلت مستيقظا؟
I want to talk to you about the wedding guests.
أريد أن أتحدث معك عن ضيوف حفل الزفاف.
Saenkaew?
ساينكاو؟
My dearest Saenkaew.
عزيزتي ساينكاو.
You're not the one who go through this.
أنت لست الشخص الذي يمر بهذا.
I'm right here.
انا هنا .
I won't let go of your hands.
لن أترك يديك.
You still have me. I love and care for you more than my own life.
مازلتُ أملكك. أحبك وأهتم بك أكثر من حياتي.
I'll try to find way for you and Ms. Rachawadee to get a marriage certificate.
سأحاول إيجاد طريقة لك وللسيدة راشاوادي للحصول على شهادة زواج.
I'll do anything for us to be together.
سأفعل أي شيء لنكون معًا.
I love him.
أنا أحبه.
I believe that you will be the last person to hurt me.
أعتقد أنك ستكون آخر شخص يؤذيني.
I feel like
انا اشعر وكأنني
I'm the luckiest girl in the world
أنا الفتاة الأكثر حظا في العالم
for having the best cousin and the best fiancé.
لأن لدي أفضل ابن عم وأفضل خطيب.
I want the three of us to stay like this forever.
أريد أن نبقى نحن الثلاثة هكذا إلى الأبد.
Sasin?
ساسين؟
I gotta go.
أنا سأذهب.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Why did your buttons look like that?
لماذا تبدو أزرارك بهذا الشكل؟
Let me help you.
دعني أساعدك.
Not true.
ليس صحيحا.
Sasin will never do that.
ساسين لن يفعل ذلك أبدًا.
When I got shot, I wasn't afraid of death,
عندما أصبت برصاصة، لم أكن خائفًا من الموت،
I was afraid that I couldn't see your face again.
كنت خائفة من أن لا أستطيع رؤية وجهك مرة أخرى.
I'm worried that my dad will hurt you again.
أنا قلق من أن والدي سوف يؤذيك مرة أخرى.
If that's the case, then I'd rather give you up,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، فأنا أفضل أن أتخلى عنك،
than having something happen to you.
من أن يحدث لك شيء ما.
I won't give up.
أنا لن أستسلم.
And you can't give up either.
ولا يمكنك الاستسلام أيضًا.
Okay?
تمام؟
Follow me.
اتبعني.
This way.
من هنا.
- Pin? - Don't say anything, my dad is coming.
- دبوس؟ - لا تقل شيئًا، والدي قادم.
- This one? - That's right.
- هذا؟ - هذا صحيح.
Sasin.
ساسين.
I know that you two are making... out right now.
أعلم أنكما تتواعدان الآن.
You know what?
أتعلم؟
You two are working together to kill me cold-heartedly.
أنتما تعملان معًا لقتلي بقلب بارد.
Pin.
دبوس.
- I'm sorry. - Why did you do it?
- أنا آسف. - لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
You're like my brother.
أنت مثل أخي.
You promised to take care of me
لقد وعدت بالاعتناء بي
to stop people from hurting me.
لمنع الناس من إيذائي.
Now you're the one doing it.
الآن أنت من يفعل ذلك.
Why're you so mean to me?
لماذا أنت قاسى معي هكذا؟
So mean.
يعني جدا.
This is all my fault.
كل هذا خطئي.
If you don't love me,
إذا كنت لا تحبني،
why are you so nice to me?
لماذا انت لطيف معي هكذا؟
Why're you making me love you?
لماذا تجعلني أحبك؟
I love you as my sister.
انا احبك كأختي.
I've never meant to hurt you, I've only meant good intention to you.
لم أقصد أبدًا أن أؤذيك، كل ما أقصده هو النية الطيبة لك.
But I really can't be your husband.
ولكنني لا أستطيع أن أكون زوجك حقًا.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
We didn't mean to hide it from you.
لم نكن ننوي أن نخفي ذلك عنك.
I'm trying to find a way to stop the wedding.
أحاول إيجاد طريقة لإيقاف الزفاف.
Then I will tell you.
ثم سأخبرك.
If you get married, you will be in so much more pain than this.
إذا تزوجت، فسوف تعاني من ألم أكبر من هذا بكثير.
I should thank you?
هل يجب علي أن أشكرك؟
And be grateful for your generosity?
وكن شاكرا لكرمك؟
He didn't mean it like that.
لم يقصد ذلك بهذه الطريقة.
We still love you.
مازلنا نحبك.
Why does your love
لماذا حبك
hurt me so much?
تؤلمني كثيرا؟
I thought that I was the luckiest woman in the world
اعتقدت أنني أسعد امرأة في العالم
with the best cousin
مع أفضل ابن عم
and the best fiancé.
وأفضل خطيب.
It turned out that I was too stupid to realize that
لقد اتضح أنني كنت غبيًا جدًا لدرجة أنني لم أدرك ذلك
two men that I loved the most
رجلين أحببتهما أكثر من أي شيء آخر
were falling in love with each other.
كانوا يقعون في الحب مع بعضهم البعض.
Pin?
دبوس؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I know that I did the wrong thing to you.
أعلم أنني فعلت الشيء الخطأ معك.
I'm trying to fix it.
أحاول إصلاحه.
I'll call off the wedding
سأقوم بإلغاء حفل الزفاف
and I'll tell everyone that it's my fault.
وسأخبر الجميع أن هذا خطئي.
I won't let the damage reach you.
لن أسمح للضرر أن يصل إليك.
And you two will be together?
وهل ستكونان معاً؟
Congrats.
تهاني.
You understand me, right?
أنت تفهمني، أليس كذلك؟
All you want is for me to understand you.
كل ما تريده هو أن أفهمك.
Does anyone understand me or feel my pain?
هل هناك من يفهمني أو يشعر بألمي؟
- Anyone? - I'm sorry.
- هل من أحد؟ - أنا آسف.
You think you can take Saenkaew away from me?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع أن تأخذ ساينكاو مني؟
No way.
مستحيل.
I'll marry him.
سأتزوجه
- Pin? - I won't call off the wedding.
- دبوس؟ - لن ألغي حفل الزفاف.
Pin?
دبوس؟
Why would you do that?
لماذا تريد أن تفعل ذلك؟
You know that I can't love you.
أنت تعلم أنني لا أستطيع أن أحبك.
I will end up in pain no matter what.
سأنتهي بالألم مهما كان الأمر.
So I should just get married.
لذا يجب علي أن أتزوج.
And all three of us
وكلنا الثلاثة
will end up in pain together.
سوف ينتهي الأمر بالألم معًا.
You don't need to come to my wedding.
لا داعي لحضور حفل زفافي.
You should stay home and rest.
ينبغي عليك البقاء في المنزل والراحة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
We can't decide who to love
لا يمكننا أن نقرر من نحب
in this world
في هذا العالم
or how our love should be like.
أو كيف ينبغي أن يكون حبنا.
You have a chance to be happy
لديك فرصة لتكون سعيدا
for yourself.
لنفسك.
But my happiness
ولكن سعادتي
and being myself hurt people.
وكوني أنا أؤذي الناس.
It hurts people I love.
إنه يؤلم الأشخاص الذين أحبهم.
It's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
You're just being yourself.
أنت فقط تكون نفسك.
You're not hurting anyone.
أنت لا تؤذي أحدا.
Stop the car.
أوقف السيارة.
Stop the car!
أوقف السيارة!
Why do you want to stop the car? You forgot something?
لماذا تريد إيقاف السيارة؟ هل نسيت شيئًا؟
Saenkaew!
ساينكاو!
Why're you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I don't want to leave you.
لا أريد أن أتركك.
But…
لكن…
I shouldn't have come back, what if my dad follows me here?
لا ينبغي لي أن أعود، ماذا لو تبعني والدي إلى هنا؟
What if he decided to kill you?
ماذا لو قرر قتلك؟
It's okay.
لا بأس.
It's okay. I'm gonna be fine.
لا بأس، سأكون بخير.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
We'll get through this.
سوف نتجاوز هذا.
I promise you.
أعدك.
I won't let go of your hands,
لن أترك يديك
even if I have to die.
حتى لو كان علي أن أموت.
Don't say that.
لا تقل ذلك.
How do I live without you?
كيف أعيش بدونك؟
Prince Inthorn was out of his mind
لقد كان الأمير إنثورن خارجًا عن عقله
for accusing that there's something going on between Sasin and Saenkaew.
لاتهامهم بأن هناك شيئًا ما يحدث بين ساسين وساينكايو.
How could it be possible?
كيف يمكن أن يكون ذلك ممكنا؟
This is all complicated.
كل هذا معقد.
Sasin got shot,
ساسين أصيب برصاصة
Saenkaew's letter
رسالة ساينكاو
and what Prince Inthorn said.
وما قاله الأمير إنثورن.
I can't let that happen.
لا أستطيع أن أسمح بحدوث ذلك.
It's embarrassing enough to
إنه أمر محرج بما فيه الكفاية
be related to a homeless prince,
أن تكون على صلة بأمير بلا مأوى،
let alone being involved with a homosexual.
ناهيك عن التورط مع شخص مثلي الجنس.
Come in.
ادخل.
This way, please.
من هنا من فضلك.
Mr. Kuea?
السيد كروس؟
Why didn't you tell me that you'd come? I would have prepared to welcome you.
لماذا لم تخبرني بقدومك؟ كنت سأستعد لاستقبالك.
I just got back from my trip abroad.
لقد عدت للتو من رحلتي إلى الخارج.
I just heard that your daughter is about to get married.
لقد سمعت للتو أن ابنتك على وشك الزواج.
That's right. Tomorrow.
هذا صحيح. غدا.
I'm sorry that I didn't invite you, I…
أنا آسف لأنني لم أدعوك، أنا...
We're busy organizing the wedding reception.
نحن مشغولون بتنظيم حفل الزفاف.
But we prepared an invitation for you, here.
ولكننا أعددنا لك دعوة هنا.
Please come.
من فضلك تعال.
I heard that your future son-in-law is a prince or some sort.
سمعت أن صهرك المستقبلي هو أمير أو ما شابه.
He's super rich, right?
إنه غني جدًا، أليس كذلك؟
So about your loan?
فماذا عن قرضك؟
- You'll get your money back, including interest. - Good.
- سوف تحصل على أموالك مرة أخرى، بما في ذلك الفوائد. - جيد.
I'll come here and collect my money tomorrow.
سآتي إلى هنا وأحصل على أموالي غدًا.
I hope you won't let me down.
أتمنى أن لا تخذلني.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
I won't be so kind anymore.
لن أكون لطيفًا بعد الآن.
Well, please come to the wedding tomorrow.
حسنًا، من فضلك تعال إلى حفل الزفاف غدًا.
You'll get your money back for sure.
سوف تحصل على أموالك بالتأكيد.
It is how it is,
إنه كما هو الحال
they need to get married no matter what.
إنهم بحاجة إلى الزواج مهما كان الأمر.
If I don't have money to return to him,
إذا لم يكن لدي المال للعودة إليه،
he'll kill me for sure.
سوف يقتلني بالتأكيد.
What if Prince Saenkaew was
ماذا لو كان الأمير ساينكاو
a homosexual like what Prince Inthorn said,
مثلي الجنس كما قال الأمير إنثورن،
what're we gonna do?
ماذا سنفعل؟
If that's true,
إذا كان هذا صحيحا،
it could be good for us.
ربما يكون جيدا بالنسبة لنا.
Sasin.
ساسين.
We've been thinking if we should ask you this.
لقد كنا نفكر فيما إذا كان ينبغي لنا أن نسألك هذا.
About you and Prince Saenkaew.
عنك وعن الأمير ساينكاو.
When we got back home last night,
عندما عدنا إلى المنزل الليلة الماضية،
we saw you and him..
لقد رأيناك ورأيناه.
That's right. We're in love.
هذا صحيح. نحن في الحب.
What?
ماذا؟
What about Pin?
ماذا عن بين؟
She's gonna marry him tomorrow, isn't she?
إنها ستتزوجه غدًا، أليس كذلك؟
Saenkaew and I tried to cancel the wedding.
لقد حاولت أنا وساينكايو إلغاء حفل الزفاف.
Pin followed Saenkaew here.
تم متابعة Pin من قبل Saenkaew هنا.
And she knows everything.
وهي تعرف كل شيء.
Still, she insisted on getting married with him.
ومع ذلك، أصرت على الزواج منه.
What?
ماذا؟
- How could they get married when Saenkaew is homo...? - Hey!
- كيف يمكنهما أن يتزوجا عندما يكون ساينكاو مثليًا...؟ - هي!
I understand if you would be disgusted by me.
أتفهم أنك ستشعر بالاشمئزاز مني.
That's right, you're disgusting.
هذا صحيح، أنت مقزز.
Hey!
يا!
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'll pack up and find another place to live.
سأجمع أمتعتي وأبحث عن مكان آخر للعيش فيه.
You have so many disgusting traits.
لديك الكثير من الصفات المثيرة للاشمئزاز.
Foul mouth,
فم كريه
too much ego, never listens to anyone, unreliable,
غرور شديد، لا يستمع لأحد أبدًا، غير موثوق به،
and so many more.
والكثير غير ذلك.
But not you loving Prince Saenkaew.
ولكنك لا تحب الأمير ساينكاو.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
No matter who you love, men or women,
بغض النظر عمن تحب، رجالاً أو نساءً،
it's none of my business. You're still my buddy.
هذا ليس من شأني. أنت لا تزال صديقي.
You're mine too.
أنت لي أيضا.
You're my brother.
أنت أخي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank you for understand me.
شكرا لك على فهمي.
I don't understand about what's going on between you two.
لا أفهم ما الذي يحدث بينكما.
And I don't have to.
ولا داعي لي ذلك.
It's your life.
إنها حياتك.
I'm on your side even though I don't understand anything.
أنا في صفك حتى لو لم أفهم شيئا.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
Let me in!
دعني ادخل!
I'm here to tell you to be prepared.
أنا هنا لأخبرك أن تكون مستعدًا.
After the wedding, you and Pin-anong
بعد الزفاف، أنت وبين-أنونغ
need to get a marriage certificate on Monday at the district office.
يجب الحصول على شهادة الزواج يوم الاثنين في مكتب المنطقة.
Then we'll travel to Chaing Mai soon after.
ثم سنسافر إلى شيانج ماي بعد ذلك قريبًا.
Why is it so sudden?
لماذا الأمر مفاجئ جداً؟
If it wasn't a holiday today,
لو لم يكن اليوم عطلة،
I would push you to get a marriage certificate today.
سأحثك على الحصول على شهادة زواج اليوم.
Please, dad.
من فضلك يا أبي.
You know that I can't marry her.
أنت تعلم أنني لا أستطيع الزواج منها.
And you expect me to host a wedding for you and Sasin?
وتتوقع مني أن أقيم حفل زفاف لك ولساسين؟
How did Inthorn find out about
كيف اكتشف إنثورن ذلك؟
your disgusting behavior?
سلوكك المثير للاشمئزاز؟
You really know what we did?
هل تعلم حقا ماذا فعلنا؟
- I can fill you in. - Saenkaew!
- يمكنني أن أخبرك. - ساينكاو!
Why? You're my father,
لماذا؟ أنت أبي.
don't you want to know your son?
ألا تريد أن تعرف ابنك؟
- What is he like? - But who you are
- كيف هو؟ - ولكن من أنت؟
and what you want
وماذا تريد
are about to destroy your family and your life.
على وشك تدمير عائلتك وحياتك.
It's not.
ليست كذلك.
You're destroying my life.
أنت تدمر حياتي.
You can hate me
يمكنك أن تكرهني
or don't see me as your dad all you want.
أو لا تراني كأبيك كما تريد.
But you need to think about others in our family,
لكن عليك أن تفكر في الآخرين في عائلتنا،
think about your grandma.
فكر في جدتك.
If she finds out about this,
إذا علمت بهذا الأمر،
you can lose her,
يمكنك أن تخسرها
like you lose your mom.
كأنك فقدت أمك.
If you continue to be stubborn,
إذا واصلت العناد،
you can prepare to go to Sasin's funeral.
يمكنك الاستعداد للذهاب إلى جنازة ساسين.
I'll go shopping for something for Chiang Mai.
سأذهب للتسوق لشراء شيء ما لمدينة شيانغ ماي.
Do you need anything?
هل تحتاج إلى أي شيء؟
- You need to go with her. - No need to.
- عليك أن تذهب معها. - لا داعي لذلك.
He should stay here and pack up.
ينبغي عليه البقاء هنا وحزم أمتعته.
Don't you worry.
لا تقلق.
No matter what happens.
لا يهم ماذا يحدث.
I will still marry him.
سأتزوجه على كل حال.